<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Yahoo! Finance: MFC.TO News</title><copyright>Copyright (c) 2016 Yahoo! Inc. All rights reserved.</copyright><link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=mfc.to</link><description>Latest Financial News for MANULIFE FIN</description><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 21:16:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><image><url>http://l.yimg.com/a/i/brand/purplelogo/uh/us/fin.gif</url><title>Yahoo! Finance: MFC.TO News</title><link>http://finance.yahoo.com/q/h?s=mfc.to</link><width>144</width><height>45</height></image><item><title>John Hancock Hedged Equity &amp; Income Fund Required Notice to Shareholders - Sources of Distribution Under Section 19(a)</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-hedged-equity-income-211600997.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - This notice provides shareholders of the John Hancock Hedged Equity &amp; Income Fund (HEQ) with important information concerning the distribution declared on December 1, 2016, and payable on December 30, 2016.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3185120523</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2016 21:16:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Asset Management Concludes Another Successful Year</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-asset-management-concludes-another-130000872.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - TORONTO and BOSTON, Dec. 28, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- Manulife Asset Management, the investment management arm of Manulife, is concluding another strong year, with growth in both sales and assets under management. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/863650655</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Tax-Advantaged Dividend Income Fund And John Hancock Tax-Advantaged Global Shareholder Yield Fund Announce Results From Special Meeting Of Shareholders</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-tax-advantaged-dividend-213100047.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - BOSTON, Dec. 22, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- John Hancock Tax-Advantaged Dividend Income Fund (NYSE: HTD) and John Hancock Tax-Advantaged Global Shareholder Yield Fund (NYSE: HTY) (each a "Fund"), each ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/959582748</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 21:31:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Research Reports Initiated on Insurance Stocks Power Corp of Canada, Manulife Financial, Industrial Alliance Insurance and Financial Services, and Power Financial</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://news.investornetwork.com/2016/12/22/research-reports-initiated-on-insurance-stocks-power-corp-of-canada-manulife-financial-industrial-alliance-insurance-and-financial-services-and-power-financial/?1=1&amp;1482414626</link><description /><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1160021540</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 13:50:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Announces Top Americans For 2017 Boston Marathon</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-announces-top-americans-153000415.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - BOSTON, Dec. 21, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- John Hancock Financial today announced the U.S. Elite Team for the Boston Marathon on April 17, 2017. The exceptional team, recruited to compete with a deep international ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2465107502</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 15:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Premium Dividend Fund And Tax-Advantaged Dividend Income Fund Declare Early Monthly Distributions</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-premium-dividend-fund-220500503.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - The Funds listed above have accelerated the declaration, ex-date, and record date of the regularly scheduled January distribution in order for the Funds to meet their 2016 distribution requirements for federal excise tax purposes. Premium Dividend Fund (the "Fund") declared its monthly distribution pursuant to the Fund's managed distribution plan (the "PDT Plan"). Distributions under the PDT Plan may consist of net investment income, net realized long-term capital gains, net realized short-term capital gains and, to the extent necessary, return of capital.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1641878541</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 22:05:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife appoints James D. Gallagher as General Counsel</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-appoints-james-d-gallagher-190000770.html</link><description>[CNW Group] - Manulife appoints James D. Gallagher as General Counsel</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/4193036759</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife appoints James D. Gallagher as General Counsel</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-appoints-james-d-gallagher-190000556.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - TORONTO, Dec. 20, 2016 /CNW/ - Manulife today announced that James D. Gallagher has been appointed Executive Vice President and General Counsel, effective immediately. Mr. Gallagher has been serving as Interim General Counsel since Oct. 20, and succeeds Stephen Sigurdson, who passed away last month. Mr. Gallagher becomes a permanent member of the Executive Committee, and will remain a member of Manulife's global leadership team.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1535778281</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Financial Eyes Growth Despite Stiff Competition</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-financial-eyes-growth-despite-124912688.html</link><description /><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/695394811</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 12:49:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Investments announces quarterly and monthly fund distributions</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-investments-announces-quarterly-monthly-144900656.html</link><description>[CNW Group] - Manulife Investments announces quarterly and monthly fund distributions</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2531324131</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Investments announces quarterly and monthly fund distributions</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-investments-announces-quarterly-monthly-144900367.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - C$ unless otherwise stated TSX/NYSE/PSE: MFC SEHK: 945 TORONTO, Dec. 16, 2016 /CNW/ - Manulife Investments today announced distributions for Oil Sands Sector Fund, Manulife U.S. Regional Bank Trust and ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2105820324</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 14:49:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Investments launches international ETF</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-investments-launches-international-130000975.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - BOSTON, Dec. 16, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- John Hancock Investments has expanded its exchange-traded fund (ETF) product lineup today with the launch of John Hancock Multifactor Developed International ETF. Dimensional Fund Advisors LP, a company regarded as one of the pioneers in strategic beta investing, was selected to design the underlying developed-market equity index for the new international ETF based on Dimensional's time-tested factor-based approach. "Adding an ETF focused on international investing is a logical extension of our product line, and we are pleased to be able to bring Dimensional's proven multifactor approach to investors seeking to invest in international markets," said Andrew G. Arnott, president and CEO of John Hancock Investments.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3744107269</guid><pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2016 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>McGill announces Dr. Thomas Robinson as the 2016 winner of the Bloomberg Manulife Prize for the Promotion of Active Health</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/mcgill-announces-dr-thomas-robinson-141500622.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - MONTREAL, Dec. 15, 2016 /CNW/ - McGill University, in association with Lawrence and Frances Bloomberg and Manulife, is pleased to announce that Dr. Thomas Robinson, a Stanford University professor of Pediatric Medicine and pioneer in using novel motivational techniques to combat childhood obesity, is the winner of the 2016 Bloomberg Manulife Prize for the Promotion of Active Health. Dr. Robinson is being recognized for developing a unique research program that goes beyond looking at the root causes of obesity and other health-related conditions by developing creative and sometimes unconventional interventions &#8211; from dance classes to educational courses -- and measuring their impact on diet, weight loss and other barometers of health.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2077919352</guid><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 14:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Investments Announces Change to Portfolio Management Team</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-investments-announces-change-portfolio-200000494.html</link><description>[CNW Group] - Manulife Investments Announces Change to Portfolio Management Team</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3429445835</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Investments Announces Change to Portfolio Management Team</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-investments-announces-change-portfolio-200000056.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - TORONTO, Dec. 14, 2016 /CNW/ - Manulife Investments today announced that Jaime Ramos Martin will replace Stephen Weeple, who has left Standard Life Investments (SLI), as portfolio manager of the Manulife Global Equity Unconstrained Fund and Manulife Global Equity Unconstrained Class, effective immediately. Jaime joins the five-person Global Equity Team and will report to Mikhail Zverev, Head of the Global Equity Team who has been managing assets in this strategy since 2010. The Global Equity Team at SLI draws on the research and analysis done by the broader Equity Team globally which consists of over 60 talented investment professionals.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2536146281</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 20:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Announces Return of Champions to 2017 Boston Marathon</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-announces-return-champions-150000575.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - BOSTON, Dec. 14, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- John Hancock Financial, the principal sponsor of the Boston Marathon since 1986, today announced the return of 2016 Boston Marathon champions Atsede Baysa and Lemi Berhanu Hayle of Ethiopia to defend their titles at the 121st running of the race on April 17, 2017. Additional champions returning to seek another win include Caroline Rotich of Kenya, Buzunesh Deba of Ethiopia, Meb Keflezighi of the United States, and Wesley Korir of Kenya.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/3837205540</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 15:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Investments expands its sustainable investment lineup, launching two new ESG funds</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-investments-expands-sustainable-140000419.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - The new funds, which offer exposure to the fixed-income and international equity markets, complement John Hancock Investments' existing U.S. equity-focused ESG funds. John Hancock ESG Core Bond Fund invests in both corporate and taxable municipal debt, while John Hancock ESG International Equity Fund invests in developed- and emerging-market equities across the market capitalization spectrum.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2384760252</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>John Hancock Closed-End Funds Announce Renewal Of Share Repurchase Plans</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/john-hancock-closed-end-funds-224600829.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - The Board of Trustees approved the renewal of the share repurchase plans as part of its ongoing evaluation of options to enhance shareholder value and potentially decrease the discount between the market price and the net asset value per share ("NAV") of the Funds' common shares. Under the share repurchase plans, each Fund may purchase, in the open market, between January 1, 2017 and December 31, 2017, up to an additional 10% of its outstanding common shares (based on common shares outstanding as of December 31, 2016). The share repurchase plans allow the repurchase of common shares in the open market at a discount to NAV. The plans could allow the Funds to realize incremental accretion to their NAV to the benefit of existing shareholders.</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2518416671</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 22:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Manulife Asset Management names Jamie Robertson to Portfolio Solutions Group, overseeing Canadian asset allocation</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/news/rss/story/*http://finance.yahoo.com/news/manulife-asset-management-names-jamie-155500966.html</link><description>[PR Newswire] - TORONTO, Dec. 8, 2016 /PRNewswire/ -- Manulife Asset Management has named R. James (Jamie) Robertson as a senior portfolio manager to its Portfolio Solutions Group (PSG), subject to regulatory approval. ...</description><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/2034824846</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2016 15:55:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Is Manulife Financial Corporation (USA) (MFC) A Good Stock To Buy?</title><link>http://us.rd.yahoo.com/finance/external/xinsidermonkey/rss/SIG=139n4qjm2/*http://www.insidermonkey.com/blog/is-manulife-financial-corporation-usa-mfc-a-good-stock-to-buy-500130/</link><description /><guid isPermaLink="false">yahoo_finance/1578600906</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 13:36:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>